队长。
Captain.
谢谢你,队长。
Thanks, Captain.
队长。
Captain.
等一等。
Hold on.
等一下，等一下。
Hold on, hold on.
好的，带他回来。快点，快点!快点。
Right, bring him to. Come on, hurry up! Hurry up.
好了，好了。把他带过来。
All right, all right. Bring him over here.
快点，让他排好队，排好队，排好队。
Come on, line him up, line him up, line him up.
一，二，三，来吧。带他过去。
One, two, three, come on. Bring him over.
你好，先生，我是康明斯博士。
Hello, sir. My name is Dr. Cummins.
我会好好照顾你的。
I'm going to be taking care of you.
四个男孩……腹部中了三枪。
Four for a boy... Okay, we have three shots in the abdomen.
5个结婚，6个生孩子…-他在说什么?-一胎六个
Five for a wedding, six for a birth... - What's he saying? - Six for a birth.
听起来像一首童谣。
Sounds like a nursery rhyme.
我得进去拿这些东西。
I'm gonna have to go in and get these.
抓住了他。
Hold him down.
好了，开始吧。
Okay, here we go.
一个
One.
进入第二阶段。
Going in for the second.
-听我说。-一场婚礼五个。
- Stay with me. - Five for a wedding.
-一场婚礼五个。——两个。
- Five for a wedding. - Two.
呃，呃，它碎了。
Uh, uh, it's shattered.
我得再去一次了。
I'm gonna have to go in a second time.
-好，最后一个。-一场婚礼五个…等一下，这里还有别的东西。
- Okay, last one. - Five for a wedding... Wait a minute, there's something else in here.
好了，来了。
Okay, here it comes.
好吧。
Okay.
那不是德国子弹。
That's not a German bullet.
银八。
Eight for silver.
他是如何?
How is he?
不太好，夫人。
Not so good, ma'am.
夏洛特!
Charlotte!
我有你的书。
I have your book.
爱德华，那是我的书。给它回来。
Edward, that's my book. Give it back.
-还给我!-爱德华，马上住手!
- Give it back! - Edward, stop this at once!
夏洛特。
Charlotte.
请。
Please.
你不能再取笑你妹妹了。
You must stop teasing your sister.
美味。
Delicious.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
阿娜伊斯，能帮我倒点热水吗?
Anais, would you mind preparing me some hot water?
我想洗个澡。——是的,女士。
- I'd like to take a bath. - Yes, ma'am.
嘿，你们两个最好别闹了!
Hey, you two better knock it off!
-是长辈。-我们下去听。
- It's the elders. - Let's go down and listen.
是的，我们得想个办法。
Yes, we need to find a solution.
在过去的三个星期里，更多的人加入了他们。
In the last three weeks, more have joined them.
我们知道他们在哪吗?
And do we know where they are?
他们在伍德菲尔德和戴的岩石之间扎营。
They are camped between Wood Field and Dei's Rock.
他们声称这块土地属于他们。
They claim the land belongs to them.
有人研究过这种说法的有效性吗?
Has anyone looked into the validity of this claim?
这一追溯至80年前的说法似乎确实有一定的合理性，但没有什么记录是不能改变的，对我们有利。
There does seem to be some validity to the claim that dates back 80 years, but there is nothing on record that can't be changed in our favor.
有人试过和他们谈判吗?
Has anyone tried to negotiate with them?
他们是吉普赛人,谢默斯。
They're Gypsies, Seamus.
他们声称对我们共享的大量土地拥有主权而我们已经向他们提出了放弃的条件。
They're laying claim to a sizeable amount of our shared lands and we've made them an offer to walk away.
这个报价很可观。
The offer was substantial.
他们想要土地。
They want the land.
那是不允许发生的。
That can't be allowed to happen.
在这个房间里，我们都有可能失去一些东西，所以我的建议是别在这里说。
We all have something to lose in this room, so what I'm suggesting stays in this room.
夏洛特，爱德华，你们走吧。你去。走,走。
Charlotte, Edward, off you go. Off you go. Go, go.
提供的钱被用来雇佣雇佣兵把他们从土地上赶走。
The money that was offered is used to hire mercenaries to remove them from the land.
根据我的经验，棍子的威胁通常就足够了。
In my experience, the threat of the stick is normally enough.
这片土地不是你的。
This land is not yours.
你被告知这块地不是你的!
You're being told this land is not yours!
集合你的人，离开这片土地!
Gather your people, get off the land!
我们开始吧。
Here we go.
再看另一个。
Let's take another one.
抓到这两个企图逃跑的人。
Caught these two trying to escape.
女人有这些。
Woman had these.
那个老婊子想用它们咬我。
Old whore tried to fucking bite me with them.
-她做了吗?——不。
- And did she? - Nah.
你以为你能用你的咒语和魔法大摇大摆地闯进我的国家然后想去哪儿就去哪儿吗?
You think you can just waltz into my country with your spells and magic and take whatever land you fancy?
以他们为例。
Make an example of them.
一个警告。他这种人在这里不受欢迎。
A warning. His kind aren't welcome 'round here.
一定要把这些和她一起埋了。
Make sure you bury these with her.
你确定吗?
You sure?
银。值一大笔钱。
Silver. Worth a pretty penny.
没有任何价值。就死亡。
There's no worth in it. Just death.
让他们离开我的视线!
Get 'em outta my sight!
来吧!
Come on!
把他放在那里。
Put him there.
现在，让我给你穿上一件漂亮的外套。
Now, let's get you in a nice coat.
是的，把它戴上。
Yeah, put that on.
好了。
There we go.
我们可不想让你着凉，对吧?
We don't want you getting cold, do we?
你得在外面待一阵子。
You're gonna be out here a while.
这是给你的教训，用你那肮脏的吉普赛嘴跟我的船长说话。
Now, this'll teach you to run your filthy Gypsy mouth to my captain.
给你穿上这个。
Let's get this on you.
来吧!灰尘很快。
Come on! Dirt soon enough.
关闭它。
Shut it.
♪翻过这山来
♪ Come over the hills ♪
♬我美丽的爱尔兰姑娘
♪ My bonnie Irish lass ♪
♪到你的爱人身边来吧
♪ Come over the hills to your darling ♪
♪你自己选择的路，爱
♪ You choose the road, love, ♪
♪。我会发誓。♪
♪ and I'll make the vow ♪
♪我将永远是你的真爱♪
♪ And I'll be your true love forever ♪♪
很好。
Very nice.
现在该睡觉了。
Now time for bed.
我想要一间房间过夜。
I'd like a room for the night.
所有的客人都必须在这里登记。
All guests must sign in here.
说明你到过哪里，要去哪里，以及你的业务。
State where you've been, where you're going, and state your business.
小镇的规则。
Town rules.
有吉普赛人在附近的报告吗?
Any reports of Gypsies in the area?
我说了，把你的事说出来。
Like I said, state your business here.
除此之外，食物和啤酒都是免费的。
Other than that, food and ale are included with the room.
请坐，我给你拿点吃的。
Take a seat, I'll bring you some food.
这并没有花很长时间。
That didn't take very long.
是什么出卖了我?
What gave me away?
除了你问的是吉普赛人的事还有你在留言簿上注明你的职业是病理学家，没什么别的。
Other than the fact you're asking about Gypsies and you stated your profession as pathologist in the guest book, not much.
这位好警官不是有事情要处理吗?
Doesn't the good constable have matters to attend to?
这是中尉。
It's lieutenant.
哦，晋升的阶梯。
Oh, climbing the promotion ladder.
给我留下了深刻的印象。
I'm impressed.
我听说了在Gévaudan发生的事。
I heard what happened in Gévaudan.
我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
你过得怎么样?
How have you been?
您打算住多久?
How long will you be staying?
我们需要一个好的病理学家。
We could use a good pathologist 'round here.
最后一个是霍乱。
Cholera got the last one.
如果霍乱是你唯一需要监管的东西，那你就不需要病理学家了，对吧?
Well, if cholera's the only thing you have to police, then you don't need a pathologist, do you?
爱德华!
Edward!
——爱德华!——爱德华!
- Edward! - Edward!
爱德华!
Edward!
爱德华,进去。介绍你自己!
Edward, come inside. Cover yourself!
发生了什么事?
What happened?
四个男孩。婚礼五张，生孩子六张。
Four for a boy. Five for a wedding, six for a birth.
七个是埋在地下的诅咒。
Seven for a curse that's buried in the Earth.
八比银，九比金。
Eight for silver, nine for gold.
十块钱买一只狼，你不会老的。
Ten for a wolf and you won't die old.
来吧，蒂米，该你了。
Come on, Timmy, it's your go.
一个是悲伤，两个是快乐，三个是女孩，四个是男孩。
One for sorrow, two for joy, three for a girl, four for a boy.
婚礼五张，生孩子六张。
Five for a wedding, six for a birth.
七个是埋在地下的诅咒。
Seven for a curse that's buried in the Earth.
我已经看到它了。
I've seen it.
见过什么?
Seen what?
在我们继续前进之前，你必须发誓不告诉任何人。
Before we go any further, you must swear not to tell anyone.
我是认真的，如果你父亲发现了，他会把我的家人赶出和解协议。
I mean it, your father will banish my family from the settlement if he finds out.
——我发誓。——我们发誓。
- I swear. - We swear.
我们不应该在这里。
We're not supposed to be here.
-长老们不允许。-自从那晚这块地着火以后，他们就禁止这样做了。
- The elders forbid it. - They have forbid it ever since the night this field was on fire.
但从那时起…你们有多少人梦见过稻草人和银牙?
But since then... how many of you have dreamt about the scarecrow and the silver teeth?
让我们把这箱财宝挖出来吧。
Let's dig up the box of treasure.
——你害怕。——不!
- You're scared. - Am not!
是的,你是。
Yes, you are.
——面对。-放开他。
- Scaredy-cat. - Leave him alone.
你要把它挖出来吗?
Are you gonna dig it up?
如果你这么勇敢，为什么不把它挖出来?
If you're so brave, why don't you dig it up?
好吧。
All right.
——我会的。-不，蒂米，不要。
- I will. - No, Timmy, don't.
提米。
Timmy.
提米,不要。
Timmy, don't.
别碰他，埃迪!
Don't touch him, Eddie!
跑,夏洛特,跑!
Run, Charlotte, run!
离开这里，快跑!
Get out of here, run!
的帮助!
Help!
夏洛特!
Charlotte!
夏洛特，怎么了?
Charlotte, what's the matter?
它是什么?发生了什么事?
What is it? What's happened?
获取医生。
Fetch the doctor.
发生了什么事?他怎么了?
What's happened? What happened to him?
亲爱的，勇敢点，亲爱的。
Darling, just be brave, dear.
在这里。
Here.
这里太黑了。
It's very dark in here.
是的，光线，刺痛了他的眼睛。
Yes, the light, it was hurting his eyes.
正确的。
Right.
我们来看看，好吗?
Let's have a look, shall we?
嗯嗯。
Mm-hm.
爱德华被某种野生动物咬了。
Edward has been bitten by some kind of wild animal.
伤口似乎感染了，而且他发烧了。
The wound does seem to be infected and he has a fever.
我治疗了他的伤口，给了他一些药，让他冷静下来。
I've treated the wound and given him something to, uh, calm him down.
我一两天内会回来看看他。
I shall come back in a day or two and check on him.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
这里。
This way.
谢谢你,医生。
Thank you, Doctor.
快跑!
Run!
爱德华?
Edward?
埃迪?
Eddie?
这是爱德华。
It's Edward.
他有点不对劲。
There's something wrong with him.
待在这里。
Stay here.
爱德华?
Edward?
爱德华!
Edward!
莫里哀。
Molière.
你是来吹嘘又一次晋升的吧?
Come to boast about another promotion, have you?
从这里骑半天就能到一个庄园。
There's a manor house half a day's ride from here.
他们的儿子失踪了，他们派人来找我。
They've sent for me regarding their son who's gone missing.
那跟我有什么关系?
And what's that to do with me?
不久以前，吉普赛人也有过这样的问题。
There was a Gypsy problem that way not so long ago.
这可能和你一直在寻找的东西有关。
It may be connected to what you've been looking for.
嘘!
Psst!
提米?
Timmy?
爱德华出外勤时发生了什么?
What happened to Edward in the field?
你不记得了?
You don't remember?
我只记得他的银牙，然后是一场噩梦，然后…然后，我在地上醒来。
What I remember was the silver teeth and then a nightmare, and then... and then, I woke up on the ground.
你用牙齿咬了爱德华。
You used the teeth to bite Edward.
你和其他人告诉他们发生了什么吗?
Did you and the others tell them what happened?
不。
No.
我们发过誓的，记得吗?
We took an oath, remember?
犹大说、我把他交给你们、你们愿意给我多少钱。
"And Judas asked, 'What are you willing to give me if I deliver him over to you?'
他们给了他三十块钱。”
And they counted out for him 30 pieces of silver."
那银子就是从前给犹大的。
It is the same silver that was given to Judas.
拿着这个，你可能用得着。
Take this, you may need it.
银在哪里?
Where's the silver?
这里的。
It's here.
在圣地。
On holy ground.
我在噩梦中看到了火焰。
I saw the flames in my nightmare.
我们都会为长辈犯下的罪付出代价。
We will all pay for the sins made by our elders.
我们都会死。
We're all going to die.
夏洛特!蒂米想要什么?
Charlotte! What did Timmy want?
来了。
Come.
爱德华!
Edward!
美好的一天,先生们。
Good day, sirs.
请跟我来。
Please, follow me.
劳伦特先生马上就来。
Mr. Laurent will be with you shortly.
先生们。谢默斯·洛朗。
Gentlemen. Seamus Laurent.
中尉阿尔弗雷德•莫里哀。
Lieutenant Alfred Molière.
-这位是病理学家。——约翰·迈克布莱德。
- This is the pathologist. - John McBride.
我们已经为您准备好了客房，以防您需要入住。
We have prepared guest rooms for you in case you need to stay.
劳伦特先生，你派人来找我们是因为你儿子失踪的紧急事件。
Mr. Laurent, you sent for us about an urgent matter regarding the disappearance of your son.
是的。
Yes.
但自从我们派人来找你，情况就变得更糟了。
But since we sent for you, things have gotten a lot worse.
耶稣。
Jesus.
死因与被野兽袭击相符。
Cause of death is consistent with attack by a wild animal.
野生动物吗?
A wild animal?
咬痕的大小和形状表明是狼咬的。
Size and shape of the bite marks suggest a wolf.
他是谁?
Who is he?
亚当斯的男孩。
The Adams boy.
你儿子仍然下落不明?
And your son is still missing?
是的。
Yes.
好。就是这样。
Well. That's that.
我这就回警局报案。
I'll head back to the department and file a report.
是它吗?
Is that it?
你被野兽袭击了。
You have an attack by a wild animal.
你的男孩的失踪。
Your boy's missing.
我不想显得冷漠，但这个国家正处于霍乱大流行之中。
I don't mean to be insensitive, but the country's in the middle of a cholera pandemic.
数以千计的人死亡。
Thousands are dead.
许多城镇正在关闭大门。
Many towns are closing their gates.
贸易路线受到严重影响。
Trade routes heavily affected.
我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
我也无能为力了。
There's nothin' more I can do.
不，如果可以的话，我想再住几天。
No, I'd like to stay on for a few days, if that's all right.
如果你的人来了就告诉我。
Let me know if your boy shows up.
这么说你认识那个男孩。
So you knew the boy.
我的儿子爱德华和女儿夏洛特经常和定居地的孩子们一起玩。
My son Edward and my daughter Charlotte often play with the children from the settlement.
爱德华失踪的那天，你还记得什么?
And on the day Edward went missing, what do you remember?
他们中的一群人曾和亚当斯的男孩一起在树林里。
A group of them had been in the woods with the Adams boy.
出了什么事，爱德华受伤了。
Something had happened and Edward had been hurt.
等我们把他送回家时，他已经开始发烧了。
And by the time we got him back to the house, he had developed a terrible fever.
有什么东西在树林里袭击了爱德华。
Something had attacked Edward in the woods.
一种动物。
An animal.
他,呃…他身上有咬痕…
He, uh... he had bite marks on his, um...
是的，它们一定来自动物。
Yes, they had to have come from an animal.
夏洛似乎很震惊。她什么都不能告诉我们。
Charlotte seemed to be in shock. She couldn't tell us anything.
那天晚上，我去看他，但他的床是空的，房子里也找不到他。
Later that evening, I went to check on him but his bed was empty and he was nowhere to be found in the house.
从那以后我们就没见过他。
We haven't seen him since.
几天后，亚当家男孩的尸体在树林里被发现。
A few days later, the body of the Adams boy was found in the woods.
麦克布莱德先生，居民区的家庭都吓坏了。
Mr. McBride, the families in the settlement are frightened.
他们受雇于我，住在我的土地上，我要对他们负责。
They are in my employ, they live on my land, and I am responsible for them.
他们指望我来解决这个问题。
They're looking to me to resolve this.
这是我的妻子，伊莎贝尔。
May I present my wife, Isabelle.
这是约翰·麦克布莱德先生。
This is Mr. John McBride.
很高兴见到你，劳伦特夫人。
Very pleased to meet you, Mrs. Laurent.
很遗憾你的爱德华失踪了。
I'm so sorry to hear your Edward is missing.
有没有可能，他只是跑掉了?——没有。
Is it possible - he's just run away? - No.
那可不像爱德华。
That wouldn't be like Edward.
你看，他是一个非常快乐的孩子。
You see, he is a very happy child.
此外，我们到处都找遍了。
Besides, we have searched everywhere.
我们还在找他。
And we are still looking for him.
请帮我们找到他。
Please help us find him.
为什么,是的…我能看看他的房间吗?
Why, yes... uh, may I see his room?
当然可以。
Of course.
我们不得不擦床单。
We had to clean the sheets.
爱德华，他…他不舒服。
Edward, he was, um... he was unwell.
我可以看看房子的其他部分吗?
May I see the rest of the house?
当然可以。
Of course.
我下来的时候，这扇门大开着。
When I came down, this door was wide open.
我们得把一楼所有的窗户都钉上。
We need to board all the windows on the ground floor shut.
为什么?
Why?
这只是预防措施。
It's just a precaution.
♬过来吧，我美丽的爱尔兰姑娘
♪ Come over the hills, my bonnie Irish lass ♪
♪到你的爱人身边来吧
♪ Come over the hills to your darling ♪
♪你自己选择的路，爱，而我会…♪♪
♪ You choose the road, love, and I'll... ♪♪
阿奈。
Anais.
夏洛特。
Charlotte.
约翰?
John?
我们会死吗?
Are we going to die?
当然不是!
Of course not!
我不能容忍餐桌上的这种谈话。
I will not stand for such talk at the table.
麦克布莱德先生是来帮我们找到爱德华的，我们可以通过保持我们的力量和坚定来帮助他。
Mr. McBride is here to help us find Edward, and we can help him by maintaining our strength and remaining steadfast.
现在,请吃。
Now, eat, please.
嗯。
Hm.
麦克布莱德吗?
McBride?
谢默斯，拿支步枪来。
Seamus, fetch a rifle.
什么样的动物会闯进别人家?
What kind of animal tries to break into houses?
有些东西我需要你帮忙。
There are some things I'm going to need from you.
这里发生了什么?
What's happening here?
我得先设个狩猎场才能确定。
Can't be sure until I set up a hunting ground.
你要猎杀它?
You're gonna hunt it?
我要召集长老们告诉他们你的计划。
I'll need to gather the elders and tell them of your plans.
我们拥有这个地区所有的土地。
We own all the land in this region.
确保他们有武装人员看守。
Make sure they travel under armed guard.
先生们，你们都知道今晚让我们来到这里的不幸情况，本地孩子被杀，我的儿子爱德华失踪。
Gentlemen, you're all aware of the unfortunate circumstances that have brought us here this evening, the killing of the local child and the disappearance of my own son, Edward.
约翰·麦克布莱德先生好心地提出要帮助抓捕杀死亚当斯男孩的动物。
Mr. John McBride has kindly offered to help capture the animal that killed the Adams boy.
你确定这是某种动物干的，不是疯子干的?
You are sure that this is some kind of animal, not the work of a madman?
在检查了尸体之后，我得出结论，死因与动物咬伤相符。
After examining the body, I concluded that the cause of death had been consistent with an animal bite.
我们说的是哪种动物?
What kind of an animal are we talking about?
狼。
Wolf.
你是一个病理学家。
You're a pathologist.
这是正确的。
That's correct.
这到底是什么意思?
What does that mean, exactly?
即使在我们死后，我们的身体也会说话。
Our body speaks even after our death.
我听。
I listen.
这不是猎人的工作吗?
Isn't it a job for hunters?
我相信我们都读过关于Gévaudan的野兽，也许听过这些故事。
I'm sure we've all read about the Beast of Gévaudan, perhaps heard the stories.
你知道，军队动乱的时候我驻扎在那里。
You see, I was stationed there during the troubles with the army.
你认为在Gévaudan发生的事情在这里也发生了吗?
You think what happened in Gévaudan is happening here?
很可能是。
It might very well be.
那么，这不是军队的工作吗?
Then, isn't this a job for the army?
不幸的是，军队可以……将……只有在确认这里发生了与Gévaudan相同的事情时才会部署。
Unfortunately, the army can... will... only be deployed if there is confirmation that the same thing is happening here as in Gévaudan.
你是在建议我们待在家里，把窗户都钉上吗?
Are you suggesting that we stay inside our house and board the windows shut?
我强烈建议。
I would strongly advise it.
在那个疯子被抓之前任何人都不该出外勤。
No one should be out in the field until that madman is caught.
抱怨是没有用的。
There's no use complaining.
我们抽签决定。
We drew the short straws.
我们搞定这事，就能回家了，好吗?
We get this done, we get ourselves home, all right?
雅各布，你去那边。
Jakob, you take the far side.
我们往里走，直到中间会合。
We'll work inwards till we meet in the middle.
睁大眼睛。在眼前。
Keep your eyes peeled. Stay in sight.
好吧?
All right?
富勒姆·?
Calum?
富勒姆·!
Calum!
雅克布?
Jakob?
快跑!
Run!
的帮助!
Help!
别人的帮助!
Somebody help!
的帮助!
Help!
我们只找到了这些。
This is all we found.
安妮玛丽和卡鲁姆，雅各布一起在地里干活。
Anne-Marie was working the fields with Calum and Jakob.
她回到了和解地点，拉响了警报。
She made it back to the settlement and raised the alarm.
我们回到这里然后…没有卡鲁姆和雅各布。
We came back here and... no Calum and no Jakob.
那女孩看到是什么袭击了他们吗?
Did the girl see what attacked them?
嗯…她震惊了。
Well... she's in shock.
什么……她说的话毫无道理。
What... what she says makes no sense.
她说什么了?
What did she say?
她说那是一条龙。
She said it was a dragon.
她的情况很糟糕，她……她失血过多。
She's in a bad way, she... she's lost a lot of blood.
她被咬吗?
She was bitten?
她在哪里呢?
Where is she?
她……她刚才还在这儿。
She... she was just here.
每个人都必须离开。
Everyone must leave.
我们不能在野外或村庄里保护他们。
We can't protect them in the field or in the village.
这里已经不安全了。
It's no longer safe here.
-去哪儿?-带他们去教堂，把门关上。
- And go where? - Take them to the church, barricade the door shut.
食物和水可以取用，但必须在武装护卫下。
Food and water can be fetched for, but under armed escort only.
我们必须限制这种暴露。
It is imperative that we limit this exposure.
接触吗?
Exposure?
-接触什么?-谢默斯，你和你的人正在被追杀。
- Exposure to what? - Seamus, you and your people are being hunted.
水，我需要水。
Water, I need water.
对不起。
Sorry.
哦。
Oh.
睡不着。
Can't sleep.
哦,我也没有。
Oh, me neither.
喝点什么吗?
Drink?
是的。
Yes.
伊迪丝是谁?
Who's Edith?
我的妻子。
My wife.
你有孩子吗?
Do you have children?
好像是很久以前的事了。
Seems a long time ago now.
他们不在你身边了吗?
Are they no longer with you?
我们被派驻到Gévaudan。
We'd been stationed to Gévaudan.
他们受到一只狼的骚扰。
They were plagued by a wolf.
第一周就有两人被杀，之后又有六人被杀。
Two people had been killed in the first week, six the following.
军队就是那时被征召进来的。
That's when the army had been drafted in.
有传言说狼是诅咒，如果人们想知道。
There was talk that the wolf was a curse, and if people need to know.
我第一次看到它时，它浑身是鲜血，就在我们村子外面。
The first time I saw it, it was covered in fresh blood, just outside our village.
等我回来的时候，已经…太迟了。
By the time I got back there, it was... too late.
有13人被野兽杀死。
Thirteen people had been killed by the beast.
我的妻子和女儿也在其中。
My wife and daughter were among them.
我很抱歉。
I'm so sorry.
他们抓到这只狼了吗?
Did they ever catch this wolf?
不久之后，一群吉普赛人来到Gévaudan网站。
Shortly after that, a band of traveling gypsies came to Gévaudan.
他们说，诅咒已经复仇了，将用吉卜赛银包住。
They said the curse had had its revenge and was to be contained in gypsy silver.
然后他们向西北行进，但在勒玛齐乌，这条路就变冷了。
They then traveled northwest, but the trail went cold in Le Malzieu.
吉普赛人对我丈夫的土地有所有权。
Well, the gypsies had a claim on my husband's land.
我丈夫和长辈们…够了!
My husband and the elders... That's enough!
这就够了。
That's enough.
我不想再谈诅咒了。
I want no more talk of curses.
我们把所有人都锁在教堂里，没人在田里干活。
We've locked everybody in a church, and I have nobody working the fields.
如果你是来帮忙的，那就帮帮我。
If you're here to help, then please help.
我只是想让这头野兽或者这只狼或者其他什么东西被抓住并杀死。
I just want this beast or this wolf or whatever it is captured and killed.
明天我将设置陷阱。
Tomorrow I will set the traps.
这到底是什么?
What in God's name is it?
先生们，我必须警告你们，这并不容易。
Gentlemen, I must warn you, this won't be easy.
——哦,耶稣。-天啊。
- Oh, Jesus. - Oh, my God.
安妮玛丽。-别碰它!
- It's Anne-Marie. - Don't touch it!
她走了。
She's gone.
他们再也回不来了。
They never come back the same.
这是我们现在能为她做的最好的事了，索尔。
It's the kindest thing we can do for her now, Saul.
她还是个婴儿的时候我就认识她了。
I've known her since she was a baby.
扫罗。
Saul.
扫罗!
Saul!
——扫罗!——扫罗!
- Saul! - Saul!
哦,耶稣基督!
Oh, Jesus Christ!
扫罗!
Saul!
扫罗,她开枪!
Saul, shoot her!
现在就做!
Do it now!
这就是降临在我儿子身上的命运吗?
Is this a fate that has befallen my son?
不能让伊莎贝尔知道这件事，我求你了。
Isabelle must never know about this, I beg you.
还有什么她不知道的?
What else doesn't she know about?
你常做梦吗，西莫?
Do you dream much, Seamus?
Gévaudan的土地被诅咒了。
The land of Gévaudan had been cursed.
晚上，每个人都做同样的梦。
At night, everyone had the same dream.
她是谁?
Who is she?
什么?
What?
那个女人被埋在田里。
The woman buried in the field.
女人……我不知道你在说什么。
Woman... I don't know what you're talking about.
她诅咒这片土地。
She cursed the land.
这是荒谬的。
That's absurd.
你刚才看到的是荒谬的吗?
Is what you just saw absurd?
梦，野兽。
The dreams, the beast.
你被诅咒了，从爱德华开始。
You were cursed, and it started with Edward.
爱德华?爱德华与此事无关。
Edward? Edward had nothing to do with this.
他会不停地杀人。
He will kill and keep on killing.
-爱德华是无辜的。-任何在攻击中幸存的人将会改变，直到诅咒完成它的报复。
- Edward is innocent. - Anyone who survives an attack will change until the curse has had its revenge.
报复吗?是我在为这事对我家人造成的伤害报仇!
Revenge? I am the one seeking revenge for what this thing has done to my family!
这是我开始的，所以我要结束它。
I started this, so I will finish it.
我要亲自追捕它，一劳永逸地了结它。
I will hunt it myself and put an end to it once and for all.
现在你烧了这东西…
Now you burn this thing...
…不管它是什么。
...whatever it is.
火炬。
Get the torch.
请不要离开我们，奶奶。
Please don't leave us, Nana.
继续,夏洛特。
Go on, Charlotte.
伊莎贝尔……埋在地里的那个女人是谁?
Isabelle... Who is the woman buried in the field?
这是唯一一个锁在抽屉里而不是挂在墙上的奖杯。
It's the only trophy that's kept locked in a drawer and not displayed on the wall.
我们必须找到被埋葬的东西。
We must find what was buried.
我们都梦想过能诅咒这片土地的银器。
We've all dreamt of the silver that has cursed this land.
在蒂米的尸体上，我发现了从《圣经》上撕下来的一页。
On the body of Timmy, I found a page torn from the Bible.
他知道一些关于银器的事，因为这里有一段划了线。
He knew something about the silver, as there was a passage underlined.
结3银子怎样熔化在炉中、你们也必照样熔化在城中。
"As silver is melted in the furnace, so will you be melted in its midst;
你就知道我耶和华是将忿怒倒在你身上了。
and you shall know that I, the Lord, have poured out My fury upon you."
以西结海啸。
Ezekiel 22:22.
夏洛特……你有什么能告诉我们的吗?
Charlotte... is there anything you can tell us?
任何东西吗?
Anything at all?
犹大说、我把他交给你们、你们愿意给我多少钱。
"And Judas asked, 'What are you willing to give me if I deliver Him over to you?'
他们就给了他三十块钱。”
So they counted out for him 30 pieces of silver."
梦中的银。
The silver from the dream.
你认为给犹大的是同样的银子。
You believe it was the same silver given to Judas.
银器在哪里?
Where is the silver?
麦克布莱德，开门!
McBride, open the door!
我们都为你的安全祈祷。
We've all prayed for your safety.
有些人已经和西莫一起去猎杀野兽了。
Some of the men have joined Seamus to go and hunt the beast.
我们无法控制谢默斯在做什么或做过什么。
We cannot control what Seamus is doing or has done.
我相信有办法阻止这一切。
I believe there is a way to stop this.
夏洛特……在哪里?
Charlotte... where is it?
索尔，发邮件到Molière。
Saul, send word to Molière.
必须立即部署军队。
The army must be deployed immediately.
索尔，我需要一个铁匠。
And, Saul, I need a blacksmith.
明天天一亮我们再试一次。
We'll try again tomorrow at first light.
伊莎贝尔?
Isabelle?
你看到我妻子了吗?
Have you seen my wife?
对不起,先生。
I'm sorry, sir.
你怎么了，你病了吗?
What's the matter with you, are you sick?
不,我很好。
No, I'm fine.
去把自己洗干净。
Go and clean yourself up.
一百年。
One hundred.
二百年。
Two hundred.
三百年。
Three hundred.
四百年。
Four hundred.
五百年。
Five hundred.
有人失踪吗?
Is anyone missing?
每个人都在这里。
Everybody's here.
它是什么?
What is it?
女仆在哪儿?
Where is the maid?
她在厨房，怎么了?
She's in the kitchen, why?
我想你应该离开这里。
I think you should leave here.
夏洛特，亲爱的，回你房间去。
Charlotte, darling, please go to your room.
——明天。——不,西莫。
- Tomorrow. - No, Seamus.
我们需要约翰的帮助。
We need John's help.
天一亮我们就再去打猎，结束这一切。
We'll hunt again at first light and put an end to all this.
然后空手而归，就像你今天一样。
And come back empty-handed just like you did today.
像所有的星期一样，军队试图追捕Gévaudan的野兽。
Like all the weeks the army tried to hunt the Beast of Gévaudan.
它想要的是你，谢默斯。
It's you it wants, Seamus.
你和你的家人。
You and your kin.
死或锁都没有区别。
Dead or chains makes no difference.
你不用去找它，因为它会因为你的所作所为而找你。
You don't have to go hunt for it, because it will hunt you for what you've done.
我所做的一切都是为了我的家人。
What I did I did for my family.
吉普赛人，他们对这片土地有所有权，不是吗?
The gypsies, they had a claim to the land, didn't they?
-那是我的土地。-你从他们那里偷来的!
- It was my land. - And you stole it from them!
-我失去了我的儿子!-现在你知道贪婪的代价了。
- And I lost my son! - Now you know the cost of greed.
我的妻儿因为你这样的人付出了代价!
My wife and child paid the price because of men like you!
请,请。
Please, please.
我只想找到我的爱德华。
I just want to find my Edward.
是的。
Yes.
你为什么不问问你丈夫他在哪里?
Why don't you ask your husband where he is?
出去。
Get out.
谢默斯，我一直以为我在追踪那只带走我家人的野兽。
You know, Seamus, all this time I thought I was tracking the beast that took my family.
但现在我意识到我完全错了。
But now I realize I got it all wrong.
我只是个看守者，确保在更多无辜的人被杀之前把这些东西都放回盒子里。
I'm just the caretaker, making sure it all gets put back in the box before any more innocent people are killed.
军队来之前我要待在这里。
I'm staying here until the army arrives.
我想念爱德华。
I miss Edward.
你今晚能和我一起住吗?
Can you stay with me here tonight?
当然,亲爱的。
Of course, darling.
阿?
Anais?
你看见西莫了吗?
Have you seen Seamus?
伊莎贝尔!
Isabelle!
夏洛特!
Charlotte!
夏洛特,伊莎贝尔!
Charlotte, Isabelle!
伊莎贝尔!
Isabelle!
谢默斯!
Seamus!
是谢默斯，他出去了。
It's Seamus, he's gone outside.
他出去了……发现夏洛特。
He's out... Find Charlotte.
房子着火了，快走!
The house is on fire, go!
谢默斯!
Seamus!
夏洛特。
Charlotte.
夏洛特，我们得离开这房子。
Charlotte, we must leave the house.
谢默斯!
Seamus!
西莫。
Seamus.
这是他的。
It was Anais.
我拍摄它。
I shot it.
我每晚都能看到火焰，约翰。
I see the flames every night, John.
我被咬。
I was bitten.
我将改变。
I'll change.
告诉伊莎贝尔和夏洛特我非常非常抱歉。
Tell Isabelle and Charlotte I'm so, so sorry.
不，不，等等!
No, no, wait, wait!
伊莎贝尔,夏洛特。
Isabelle, Charlotte.
来吧!
Come on!
等待,谢默斯在哪里?
Wait, where's Seamus?
我们得去教堂。
We have to get to the church.
这是唯一安全的地方。我们走吧。
It's the only safe place. Let's go.
来吧!
Come on!
我们走吧!
Let's go!
来,来,来。
Come, come, come.
娜娜吗?
Nana?
趴下，趴下。
Get down, get down.
别动，别动。
Stay still, stay still.
娜娜吗?
Nana?
夏洛特，你必须安静。
Charlotte, you must be quiet.
呆在这里。
Stay right there.
银。
Silver.
起来，起来!
Get up, get up!
快点，走，走!
Come on, move, go!
来了。
Come.
跟在我后面，朝教堂走。
Stay behind me and move towards the church.
移动,走,走。
Move, go, go.
让我们进去!
Let us in!
-让我们进去!-开门!
- Let us in! - Open the door!
打开这扇门!
Open the door!
关上门。
Close the door.
发生了什么事?
What's happened?
庄园着火了。
The manor is on fire.
和西莫?
And Seamus?
他没能活下来。
He didn't make it.
我们差点没到这儿。
We barely made it here.
它一路跟踪我们。
It stalked us the whole way.
就剩下你一个人了吗?
Were you all that is left?
Aye.
那我们现在怎么办?
So what do we do now?
——我们等待。——等待?
- We wait. - Wait?
等待什么?
Wait for what?
不，不，我厌倦了等待，厌倦了躲藏。
No, no, I'm tired of waiting, hiding.
我们就像羊。
We're like sheep.
如果你是说杀死我儿子的东西就在门外，我说，我说我们出去杀了它。
If you're telling me the thing that killed my son is just outside those doors, I say, I say we go outside and we kill it.
你要是出去，就死定了。
You go out those doors and you will be dead.
你怎么来到这里的?你没有死。
How come you made it here? You're not dead.
我有它害怕的东西。
I have something it's afraid of.
什么?
What?
我有灵丹妙药。
I have the silver bullet.
但我们得等到天亮，把它引到开阔的地方，然后瞄准。
But we have to wait for daylight, draw it into the open and have a clean shot.
这是我们唯一的希望。
That is our only hope.
我们收到通知Molière。
We got word to Molière.
军队明早就会到。
The army will be here by morning.
——这很好。——现在休息。
- That's good. - Now rest.
今晚还有很长的路要走。
We've got a long night ahead of us.
我相信这是你儿子的。
I believe this belonged to your boy.
谢默斯怎么了?
What happened to Seamus?
这是他的。
It was Anais.
我到他那里时，他受了重伤。
He was badly wounded when I got to him.
他让我告诉你和夏洛特他很抱歉。
He told me to tell you and Charlotte... that he was sorry.
爱德华在这场噩梦中迷失了吗?
Is Edward lost to this nightmare?
我不能说。
I can't say.
我子民的罪孽玷污了。
The sins of my people have soiled.
但现在我以母亲的身份来找你，请原谅我的悲伤。
But now I come to you as a mother, aching the weight of my grief, please.
我能给你的一切，任何道路，请告诉我，求你了。
Anything I can give, any path, please show me, I beg you.
饶了我们吧，如果还有希望，请饶了我。
Show us mercy, if there is any hope, please show me.
求你，主，怜悯我们吧。
I beg you, Lord, show us mercy.
求你别离开我们，别走!
Please don't leave us, don't go!
请妈妈!
Please, Mother!
爱德华。
Edward.
妈妈，求你了，求你了，快来救我!
Mother, please, please, come get me!
妈妈!
Mother!
爱德华。
Edward.
爱德华,我来了。
Edward, I'm coming.
伊莎贝尔!
Isabelle!
不!
No!
妈妈!
Mother!
回来!
Get back!
动!
Move!
够了!
Enough!
——伊莎贝尔。- - - - - -爱德华。
- Isabelle. - Edward.
让开。
Move out of the way.
快来接我!
Please come get me!
不。
No.
我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
把他们从教堂地板上捡起来。
Picked them up off the church floor.
他什么都不记得了。
He doesn't remember anything.
爱德华。
Edward.
的儿子。
Son.
你和你妹妹现在要来和我住在一起。
You and your sister are going to come and live with me now.
好吧?
All right?
这一切都不是你的错，儿子。
None of this was your fault, son.
好吧。
All right.
你去。
Up you go.
夏洛特。
Charlotte.
它的时间。
It's time.
♪翻过这山来
♪ Come over the hills ♪
♬我美丽的爱尔兰姑娘
♪ My bonny Irish lass ♪
♪翻过这山来
♪ Come over the hills ♪
♪给你心爱的♪
♪ to your darling ♪
♪你自己选择的路，爱自己
♪ You choose the road, love ♪
♪我发誓
♪ And I'll make a vow ♪
♪我会是你的真爱
♪ That I'll be your true love ♪
永远
♪ forever ♪♪